("Crazy In Love" by Beyonce ft. Jay Z)
♪ Yes ♪
♪ So crazy right now ♪
♪ Most incredibly it's your girl B ♪
♪ It's your boy Young ♪
♪ You ready ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh no no ♪
♪ Geah history in the making ♪
♪ Part two ♪
♪ It's so crazy right now ♪
♪ I look and stare so deep in your eyes ♪
♪ I touch on you more
and more every time ♪
♪ When you leave I'm
begging you not to go ♪
♪ Call your name two
three times in a row ♪
♪ Such a funny thing for
me to try to explain ♪
♪ How I'm feeling and my
pride is the one to blame ♪
♪ 'Cause I know I don't understand ♪
♪ Just how your love can
do what no one else can ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy right now ♪
♪ Your love's got me
looking so crazy right now ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy right now ♪
♪ Your touch got me looking
so crazy right now ♪
♪ Got me hoping you'll page me right now ♪
♪ Your kiss got me hoping
you'll save me right now ♪
♪ Looking so crazy your
love's got me looking ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy in love ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh no no ♪
♪ When I talk to my friends so quietly ♪
♪ Look at what you did to me ♪
♪ Tennis shoes don't even
need to buy a new dress ♪
♪ If you ain't there ain't
nobody else to impress ♪
♪ It's the way that you
know what I thought I knew ♪
♪ It's the beat that my heart
skips when I'm with you ♪
♪ But I still don't understand ♪
♪ Just how your love can
do what no one else can ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy right now ♪
♪ Your love's got me
looking so crazy right now ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy right now ♪
♪ Your touch got me looking
so crazy right now ♪
♪ Got me hoping you'll page me right now ♪
♪ Your kiss got me hoping
you'll save me right now ♪
♪ Looking so crazy your
love's got me looking ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy in love ♪
♪ I'm looking so crazy your
love's got me looking ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy in love ♪
♪ Young Hov y'all know
when the flow is loco ♪
♪ Young B and the R-O-C uh-oh ♪
♪ OG Big Homie the one and only ♪
♪ Stick bony but the
pockets is fat like Tony ♪
♪ Soprano the ROC handle like Van Exel ♪
♪ I shake phonies man
you can't get next to ♪
♪ The genuine article
I do not sing though ♪
♪ I sling though if anything I bling yo ♪
♪ A star like Ringo war
like a Green Beret ♪
♪ You crazy Bring ya whole set ♪
♪ JAY-Z in the Range crazy and deranged ♪
♪ They can't figure him out
they like hey is he insane ♪
♪ Yes sir I'm cut from a different cloth ♪
♪ My texture is the best fur chinchilla ♪
♪ I've been iller than chain smokers ♪
♪ How you think I got the name Hova ♪
♪ I been realer the game's over ♪
♪ Fall back Young ♪
♪ Ever since I made the
change over to platinum ♪
♪ The game's been a wrap one ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy my baby ♪
♪ I'm not myself lately I'm
foolish I don't do this ♪
♪ I've been playing
myself baby I don't care ♪
♪ 'Cause your love's got the best of me ♪
♪ And baby you're making a fool of me ♪
♪ You got me sprung and
I don't care who sees ♪
♪ 'Cause baby you got me you got me ♪
♪ You got me you got me so crazy baby ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy right now ♪
♪ Your love's got me
looking so crazy right now ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy right now ♪
♪ Your touch got me looking
so crazy right now ♪
♪ Got me hoping you'll page me right now ♪
♪ Your kiss got me hoping
you'll save me right now ♪
♪ Looking so crazy your
love's got me looking ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy in love ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy right now ♪
♪ Your love's got me
looking so crazy right now ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy right now ♪
♪ Your touch got me looking
so crazy right now ♪
♪ Got me hoping you'll page me right now ♪
♪ Your kiss got me hoping
you'll save me right now ♪
♪ Looking so crazy your
love's got me looking ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy in love ♪